myebiz.com 2007-10-10

# _

## PRIVACY POLICY

Effective Date: April, 2007.

Please note: our privacy policy changes from time to time. Please check back frequently for updates.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

The information collection, use, and dissemination practices of My E Biz (the "Company") are discussed in this policy. This policy applies to Company's information collection (a) on Company's websites, (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to Company's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties.

**The Information We Collect**

**Non-Identifiable Information**

We collect information through technology to make our site more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to one of our sites, we collect your IP address. An IP address is often associated with the portal through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP (Internet Service Provider). Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our site.

We also collect the anonymous information through the use of "cookies." A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Some features of our website use cookies to better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of our website may not function properly.

Web bugs. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using an programming function -- see www.w3.org for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. If you wish more information about web bugs, you may wish to visit http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/W/Web_beacon.html

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Much of the personally identifiable information we receive comes directly from website visitors who voluntarily completes a Company survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). In the Surveys, the Company or a third party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to the Company, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). 

**Payment Information**

The Company may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from Company. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to Company, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. The Company will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

**Our Commitment to Children´s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. The Children´s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) applies to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. It is designed to ensure that parents are in control over what information is collected from children under 13. For that reason, we never collect information at our website from those we actually know are under 13. Any information about a child under the age of 13 must be submitted by the child´s parent or legal guardian.

The Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If the Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. 

**How Your Information Is Used**

**Summary Data.**

The Company may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

**Order Fulfillment.**

The Company will transfer Individual Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such third party while using Company web sites or when responding to offers provided by Company.

**Discretion to Use Information.**

THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs describe how the Company currently uses Individual Information, but the Company may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, the Company may update this policy from time to time. The Company may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

**Monitoring and Recording.**

You hereby give permission and consent to Company or its affiliates to contact you via phone or email and agree to allow Company or its affiliates to monitor or record your phone conversations with Company or its affiliates. Verbal notice may not be provided of monitoring or recording.

**Use of Technology Information.**

The Company uses technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Company's web sites are most frequently visited. This information helps the Company to better understand the online habits of individuals so that the Company can target advertising and promotions to them.

**Profiles of Individuals.**

The Company uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.

**Sale** **or Transfer to Third Parties.**

THE COMPANY MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION.

**Changes or Updates to Collected Information and Opting Out**

You may change or update the information that you have provided us by contacting us at privacy@myebiz.com or (801) 216-8111. You may also write to us at: My E Biz, Attention: Privacy, 629 E. 730 S. Ste 103 American Fork, UT 84003. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before changing or updating any information.

You may also choose to have your name taken off our correspondence list and, thus, cease to receive correspondence from us by contacting us through one of the channels listed in the preceding paragraph.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

The Company stores the Individual Information in a database on Company computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Company's control. Notwithstanding such measures, the Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent the Company computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods.

Payment information and health information are stored in an encrypted form in a secured database. The Company uses high grade 128-bit Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encryption to protect the integrity of all credit card transmissions to our servers.

**Questions Regarding this Privacy Policy**

If you have questions or concerns about privacy issues related to this website, you may contact us at privacy@myebiz.com or (801) 216-8111. You may also write to us at: My E Biz, Attention: Privacy, 629 E. 730 S. Ste 103 American Fork, UT 84003.
